[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Morning, my tofu.
Take this!
(I’m not used to this.)
(I never thought you could do something like this.)
Well, I’m trying to win you over.
And when I’m won?
Then I might want something more.
Wanna sleep in my room?
I told Pethong to sleep in your room instead.
(Today has been so wonderful, Bay)
(I don’t want it to end.)
Tomorrow,
when you wake up,
I’ll still be here.
Sun.
Hmm?
Can I call you my boyfriend now?
You can’t wait?
Pretty much.
I want to be your boyfriend, too.
But can you wait until after PREM’S GAME?
Urg. Why?
Do we really have to wait that long?
Be patient.
Oh, there, there.
Every single match means a lot to me.
And more importantly,
this is the first match we get to play
together in 10 years.
Mmm.
I get it.
I’m not going anywhere.
Promise?
Then...
if we win PREM’S GAME,
will you be my boyfriend?
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE
How are things going on your side?
Anyone getting suspicious?
Nope.
But right now
I can’t wait to show my boyfriend off.
Easy.
Just friend.
Hey!
You’re acting weird.
Are you having a mood swing?
How am I weird?
This how I always am.
Not even close.
Nonsense.
Move.
What’s up with you?
Who are you?!
Wait.
Is that your guy?
Not that one.
Well, he’s smiling at you.
Not him.
NO ENTER
OUT OF SERVICE
Is this really gonna work?
This is all I can do.
Let’s just start training and leave
before people see you.
That’d be best, okay?
What the hell are you doing?
Well...
From that angle, my double chin
must be showing.
You cutie patootie. My tofu.
So cutesy.
Stop taking my pictures.
I said stop it.
Okay.
Loosen up, little tofu.
Come on now.
Go warm up and get to training.
Go, now.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry, before people see you.
Go, now.
Come on.
No more pictures.
Come here.
(Why are you taking so many pictures?)
(Look at me.)
(I look like a wet dog.)
(Stop it.)
(No, you’re so freaking cute.)
SETTING AND ACTIVITY
CLOSE FRIENDS LIST
Hey!
Sh*t!
Did you...
You’re gonna get us killed.
Damn it! You cut me off?
DELETE!
Delete it!
I said delete it.
We’re gonna get in trouble.
Are you insane?
Do you hear me?
NO
YOU…
Bay, listen to me. Delete it!
CUTIE
Bay, didn’t you hear me?
I said delete it.
You’re the only one in my Close Friends.
I’ve removed everyone else.
Really?
Really.
My Close Friends list is just for you, Sun.
But…
I’m still waiting to be upgraded
from a Close Friend to a boyfriend.
Yeah, yeah.
I’m…
I’m going to bed now.
You should…
go to bed, too.
Don’t stay up late.
Okay.
I’m going to bed now.
Good night.
Damn it!
I’m blushing.
You just said good night to me?
Why are you blushing?
Well, my Close Friend is just too cute.
Muah!
Damn it!
You’re so freaking cute!
What’s going on?!
Are you okay?!
Boat, I’m so down bad right now!!
See what’s happening with your student?
Is he okay?
I’m starting to worry.
When the dad’s away, the Bay will play.
So?
I think it’s kind of cute.
Well...
It took him this long to realize
he has a crush on Sun.
It’s been over ten years.
Only ten years?
Not as long as me.
Hey.
You’re having a crush on someone?
Why do you wanna know?
Fine.
You don’t have to tell me now.
But I’d say…
if you like someone,
hurry up and let them know.
Why?
‘Cause maybe they like you, too.
Woo!!
Next up, Supattra.
MY SOON-TO-BE BF IS SO TALENTED
Hey, hey, everyone.
Keep it down.
And put your phones on silent mode.
Sh*t! Bay!
MY SOON-TO-BE BF IS SO TALENTED
Sh*t!
Bay!
You didn’t post that on Close Friends!
BP 25th GEN
MY SOON-TO-BE BF IS SO TALENTED
-WHAT?
-SUN IS TAKEN
(Attention, all students and faculty.)
(We are currently in an emergency situation.)
(I, the principal, ask everyone to remain calm)
(and follow all of my instructions.)
(No exceptions.)
The whole school agreed
to keep this a secret.
And according to Coach Kong,
your fathers haven’t seen that post.
Thank you, Principal.
Why are you doing so much for us?
Because since both of you’ve been assigned as partners,
no teachers have complained about
your shenanigans.
Do you know when the last time our school was this peaceful?
I’m dead serious, Bay.
This made me realize
maybe it’s not too late
for people who can’t stand each other
to finally call a truce.
You two are a good example.
If only your fathers could do the same.
One of the reasons
I wanted you to compete in PREM’S GAME
was that I wanted you to see each other as your partner.
And secondly, I wanted you to get that trophy as proof.
Proof of what, ma’am?
Proof for your fathers to see
that when the two of you aren’t fighting,
you bring out the best in each other.
Your fathers are so stubborn.
They wouldn’t believe it without proof.
Now,
only the two of you can make that happen.
I’m counting on you.
And also...
I’d like you to know how glad I am
that both of you don’t see each other as enemies anymore.
Do you think our dads know about us?
I don’t know about that.
But I think…
If my dad finds out,
I’ll just come out to him.
Bay!
Something terrible happened.
Mom?!
What happened?
SAMING PHON FAI
-Sun!
-Yes?!
Can you get my phone checked?
Of course, Pa.
I’ll get it fixed.
Didn’t you say grandma had recovered
from cancer?
But it can come back.
And we don’t know if it can be
cured this time.
How long will you stay with grandma?
Maybe 2-3 months, right?
Mmm.
Pretty much.
Have you fixed that?
I’m trying.
Fix what?
My phone, of course.
I can’t connect to the internet for
some reason.
-IS IT TRUE ABOUT BAY AND SUN?
-PERIOD!!
-SUN IS TAKEN.
Sh*t!
What?
Your phone has a virus, dad.
I told you not to download shady apps.
Now it has all types of viruses.
Just hurry and get it fixed.
If you can’t, I’ll take it to the phone shop.
How am I gonna doomscroll now?
(Thank you so much.)
How’s that?
It was all my big bro.
What?
He sneaked into my house to mess up
my dad’s phone?
Mmm.
Okay.
That’s good.
I told my dad to put his phone in rice.
When things fizzle out, I’ll tell him
to get a new one.
But your brother…
He is something.
Other than my brothers,
people are happy for us, too.
Now that we’re together.
Check this out.
BANGKOK PIPAT SCHOOL
There’s even a Discord group.
“Protect BaySun at all costs”
They said,
they would keep it a secret
from the others at school.
Should I...
be happy about this?
Come on.
At least we can relax for a bit,
now that these people are helping us.
Easy, my friend.
I wish I could ban the word “friend”.
I’m keeping track of what you owe me.
When you’re my boyfriend,
I’ll come back and collect it.
I’ll be waiting.
What time is it now?
It’s late.
You should go home.
Do I really have to go?
Of course, or you won’t get up
in the morning.
We’ll have to get up early.
Okay.
Hey, wait.
Hmm?
Yes?
I’m counting on you tomorrow.
Of course.
I always give it my all.
Can I have my phone back, please?
I don’t want your hand.
I only want your cheek.
Quit smiling. Give it back.
See you. Bye-bye.
You want my cheek?
Here it is.
FIRST ROUND OF PREM’S GAME
Welcome, everyone, to PREM’S GAME 2026.
In today’s first round,
the tennis competition will feature both
doubles and singles matches,
for both male and female students.
No need to freak out.
We got this.
What?
Who’s freaking out?
I’m not.
No need to freak out, guys.
Your first time should be exciting.
It’s your first time, too.
You’re the one who’s freaking out.
Look.
Who are those evil twins?
Those are Kan and Kelvin.
From Grand Empire International School.
They’re the favorites in this event.
Look at them acting nonchalant.
Right.
I already hate them.
Totally.
-You hate them, too?
-I hate you.
Yas!
Yes!
Bay.
Focus.
What do you think, Coach?
I think…they can see our weak spot.
They’re only attacking Bay.
Right.
Yay!
Yay!!
Nice job.
You did great.
You can do this.
Come on.
Look here.
See?
They kept attacking Bay.
When Sun went to help him,
he left that space open.
When there’s open space on the court,
it gives the opponents an easy point.
I must be much weaker than Sun
for the opponent to notice.
Don’t say that, Bay.
You’re back after ten years.
This is good enough.
What do we do now, Coach?
Mmm.
Now...
I want you to use shadowing.
(Shadowing is about keeping distance.)
(By following your partner’s shadow)
(so Bay can train his body)
(to move at the same pace as Sun.)
Listen up.
I want you two to imagine there’s a rope
tying the two of you together.
You have to keep this rope in place.
Don’t let it go slack or get too tight.
And after that,
Bay needs to find the right moment
to hit the ball back with power,
forcing the opponent into the position we want,
and finish the job.
My tofu.
-My baby.
-Hey, who said you could do that?
Who said you could do that?
-Who said you could do that?
-Oww.
-Come here.
-Who said you could do that?
-Come on.
Who said you could do that?
Hey, dad.
You’ve been coming home late.
Been working on my portfolio.
The schools in Italy are very serious
about it.
The schools in Italy, huh?
Yes.
What’s going on with you and Sun?
What do you mean?
I don’t know.
Have you two become close now?
Why would you ask that?
It’s because…
I think I saw you
fooling around with Sun.
Oh.
I remember.
I was trying to kick his butt.
Oh.
He was getting on my nerves
so I wanted to kick him.
Teach him a lesson.
But he couldn’t fight me,
so I just laughed at him.
Nothing more?
Nothing more.
Ooh, staring contest.
You didn’t even blink.
Well, I have nothing to hide.
Well, that’s good.
Yeah.
-Don’t stay up late.
-Okay.
But I thought I saw you fooling around
with him.
Get out of here, dad.
I’m going now.
Keep your eyes on dad.
Mmm, hurry.
Is he suspicious?
What are you guys talking about? !
-Nothing!
Wow, you said that in unison.
You sure?
Yes, dad.
I was telling Boat I’m off to do my portfolio.
To do your portfolio?
Here.
I got all my equipment.
I’m leaving now.
Bye-bye.
What are you doing?
Do you think Bay is acting weird?
Has he told you anything?
You’re acting weird.
It’s nothing.
He’s just…
getting ready for his college application.
College application?
The hell is he doing?
He must have completely lost it.
PREM’S GAME FINAL DAY
Welcome to the PREM’S GAME 2026
men’s doubles tennis final.
Today’s championship match is between
Bangkok Pipat School
versus
Grand Empire International School.
-Yay!
Yes!
Woo!
Why can’t I watch anything?
Boat, have you paid the internet bill?
(I have.)
Maybe the router is busted.
Hey, dad.
I’ll take care of it. Don’t worry.
-I’ll check it out.
-Hey, it’s okay.
I’ll take care of it. You sit and rest.
Just go and fix it.
Relax, dad.
Hey, what’s wrong with this?
Have you fixed it?
Almost done, dad.
Trying.
You’re taking too long.
I’ll use my phone instead.
Yes!
Woo!
Great job!
Let’s go!
We’ve got one set.
Just one more, guys!
Go, Bay, Sun!!
Hmm?
Chun!!
What?
Why are you here?
Do you know about this?
You stop right there, Boat!
I’ll deal with you later.
(My dad and Sun’s dad just found out.)
(They’re heading there now.)
Oh, sh*t!
Guys,
I need your help.
Uncle Chun, Uncle Bee, hello.
Keaw. Zippo.
I know everything.
Where are they now?
I’ll take you there.
Hurry up.
Right this way.
Why are you so fast? Wait!
Where are you taking them?
Just four more points.
Anywhere but the tennis court.
Just go, come on!
-Are they really playing up there?!
-Up there?!
Come on!
Damn it!
This way, sir.
I’m begging you.
Give us more time.
If you’re tired, just leave.
Oh, look at you.
Put your tongue away.
I’m not a dog!!
Just try to keep up!!
-Yes!
You loser!!
I can’t run after those brats anymore!
Look!!
What?!
Yes!!
Good job!
TENNIS COURT
No, guys!
Don’t go that way.
Not that way, guys.
Bay.
Sun.
We have to finish this.
Hurry!
-Sh*t!
-Try again.
It’s all right.
Come on.
Sir,
this match is almost over.
Can we talk after the game?
It’s the last match.
I’m begging you.
Please.
I knew it.
He’s become close to Sun lately.
Hey!
My son’s never lied to me in his life.
-Yeah?
-Yeah!
Your son is a bad influence.
We’ll find out who’s in the wrong after
the game.
If it’s my son, I’ll deal with him.
Oh, please.
You guys,
I’d like you to know that
when these two are together,
or when they practice together,
they look so happy.
And now...
they’re so close to becoming champions.
What I want to say is...
I understand that you’re worried about them.
But controlling them too much
might make them feel suffocated.
So I’d like to suggest
that you take a step back
and give them some space,
while supporting them from afar.
Now let’s see how this match turns out, shall we?
Yes!
Woo!
Focus, man.
Sun!!
Focus!
You two can do this!
Bay!!
You better win this!
‘Cause you’re the son of Merlion!
I’ll show you, dad.
Okay!
If you make my son lose, you’re dead!
If you make my son lose, you’re dead, too!
Let’s go!
Focus!!
Sun…
Yes!!
That’s my boy, haha!!
Good job!!
Yay!!
And that’s my boy!
My boy!
Good job, Bay!
Good job, Bay!!
Great!
What’s wrong with you?!
Yay!!
We won!!
They did it!
They won!
What the hell?
We won! Hey!!
I finally get to pat your head.
Do it as much as you want.
This is your reward.
What about our deal?
You said, if we won,
we could be boyfriends.
Mmm.
I’ve been wondering,
the day’s almost over
why no one has asked me yet.
Will you be my boyfriend?
♪ You’re the only one I’ll ever give a Like ♪
♪ Want, want you to come and be
a part of my life ♪
♪ Morning, afternoon, or all night,
I’ll always make you smile ♪
♪ No matter how many seconds pass, I promise I’ll never make you cry ♪
Now we’re boyfriends.
♪ You’re the only one I’ll ever give a Like ♪
♪ Want, want you to come and be
a part of my life ♪
♪ Morning, afternoon, or all night,
I’ll always make you smile ♪
♪ No matter how many seconds pass, I promise I’ll never make you cry ♪
♪ I’ll hold you tight ♪
♪ Never let you out of my sight ♪
♪ Stay by my side ♪
♪ We don’t need the stars to tell us
this is real ♪
♪ We don’t have to wait for some day
they say is special ♪
♪ I'm giving you my whole heart♪
Did you lock the door this time?
♪ It’s time that we fall in love ♪
♪ It’s finally time for you and me to be in love ♪
♪ This very second belongs to you alone ♪
♪ My heartbeat says it's yours to own ♪
♪ It’s time that we fall in love ♪
♪ It’s finally time for me to put you first ♪
♪ Let’s be each other’s reason to smile every day ♪
♪ ’Cause in my heart, you’re here to stay ♪
(Are you sure you can be alone?)
(I’ll be fine, Pa.)
(I can stay there by myself.)
Surprise!
(Why did you follow me here?)
(I’m not here to play.)
(I’m here to take care of you.)
(I don’t feel comfortable)
(with you being with that boy.)
Pa!!
We’ll get through this.
‘Cause you’re my boyfriend.
♪ I admit my heart has wanted you ♪
♪ Ever since the day I first met you ♪
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION,
MINISTRY OF CULTURE